THE CAPITAL JURY PROJECT RECORDS (APAP196) 1941-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subject Files, 1941-1996; 7; 17
  - Preliminary Tabulations - Post-Furman Statutes, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Tabulations Florida - Georgia, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "The Present Significance of Race: Findings from National Surveys, 1976-1978" by Linda L. Marston and Richard Morse, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Press List, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Presbytery of the James, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Prison Info (National and International), 1969; 1980; 1983-1986; Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Project Development, 1981; Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Project on Government Oversight, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Project Hope, 1990; 1991; 1992; Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Proposal to the National Institute of Justice "The Impact of Crime on Small Business Viability: Checking 'The Boston Strangler', 1987 February 13 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Public Reactopm - Negative, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Publicity, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Publicity, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Publicity, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Publicity, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Publicity, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Publicity, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Publicity, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Publicity, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Publicity: Miscellaneous, 1976-1988; Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Publicity about Team Policing, 1982-1983; 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Publicity - C.P. Bowers, 1976-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Question Sentencing Effects on Response to Sensitive Questions in the Self-Administered Questionnaire by William J. Bowers and Russell B. Stearns, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Question Sentencing Effects on Response to Sensitive Questions in the Self-Administered Questionnaire by William J. Bowers and Russell B. Stearns, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Quetelet Research, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Quotes, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Race Disc - Data and Drafts, 1981; Undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Racial Discrimination and the Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Racial Justice Act, 1988; 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Radelet, Mike, 1986; 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Radiation, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Radon Survey, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Rantoul, Robert Jr. Correspondence and Papers Related to Capital Punishment, 1990; Undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Rape Project Preliminary Report Fisher, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Raulerson, J.D., 1979-1980; 1982-1983; 1985 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Reebok, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Remarks by Gov. William F. Weld and Related Materials, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Repeat Call, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Report Requests Filled: Capital Punishment in Incremental Evaluation of Discrimination, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Report Requests Filled: Deterrence, Brutalization or Nonsense?, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Report Requests Filled: Prelim. Tabs, re: Arbitrariness and Discrimination Under Post-Furman Statutes, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Requests: Preliminary Tabs Discrimination, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Report to the Deputy Attorney General on Capital Punishment and Sentencing Commission, 1987 February 13 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Requests for Reprints, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Research, 1986; Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Resource Centers Reference Guide, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Research Committee Materials, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Research on Commuted, 1965; 1982; Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Research Conducted by Watt Espy, 1983; 1984; Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Rhode Island, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Right Livelihood Award, 1990; Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Righthand Report, 1980 March (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Robeson Defense Committee, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Rogers/ Zampino Proposal, 1984-1985; 1988; Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Roper Center for Public Opinion Research, 1983; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Running Project, 1979-1980; 1983; Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Running Project, 1979-1980; 1983; Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Sands, Robert, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Sanford, Terry - Senator, 1987; 1990 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Santucci, Frank, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - The Saga of Shame - Let Live, Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Scanlon, Jon, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Select Oversight Committee on Corrections, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - The Sentencing Project, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Snitches, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Somoroff, Michael, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Songer, Carl, 1979-1982; 1984-1985; 1987; 1989 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons (SCJP) and Joseph P. Ingle Correspondence, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Spar-A-Con, 1987; Undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Speakers Bureau Reports, 1990; Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Spencer, George TN Illustrated, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Spivey, Ron, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Stack, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Stack, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Stack's Own Data, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Stack Repliciation - Correspondence, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Staff Letters - Copies, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Stephens v. Zant Law Opinions and Notes, 1980; 1981; Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Storms, 1941; 1949-1959; 1974-1979; 1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Strieb, Victor, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Styron, William - Author, 1984; 1987; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Student Dishonesty, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Superintendent of Florida State Prison Richard Dugger, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Supreme Court of Florida Cases and Research, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Supreme Court Death Penalty, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Survey of State Legislation, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1989; 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tables, Ca. 1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Tables: Age of Defendants in Fla, Geo, Oh, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Tables: Types of Defense Attorneys for Defendants Sentenced to Death, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Tarasoff, 1978; 1982; 1984-1986; Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Tarasoff, 1978; 1982; 1984-1986; Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Team Policing, 1986; Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Trends Questionnaire Countries, A-G, 1962; 1976; Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Trends Questionnaire Countries, H-N, 1967-1977; Undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Trends Questionnaire Countries, P-Z, 1976; Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Torch of Conscience Massachusetts Steering Committee, 1989; Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Total Population, 1985, Ca. 1987 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - UCR Proposal, Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - US Department of Justice - Statistics Bulletin on Capital Punishment, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - US General Accounting Office Report to Senate and House Committees on the Judiciary of Death Penalty Sentencing, 1990 February (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - The University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Data Sheets, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - "Unreliability in Aggrevated Assault Statistics Implications and Recommendations" by Glenn L. Pierce and William J. Bowers, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Updating Boston Urban Database, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Urgent Request for Immediate Action to Save Habeas Corpus, 1991 August 5 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Various Newspaper Clippings on the Death Penalty, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Victimization, Undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Wasserman Critique, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Weather, 1980-1983; 1986; Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Weiss Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "What is the Effect of Executions: Deterrence or Brutalization?" by William J. Bowers and Glenn L. Pierce, 1977 November (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - William J. Bowers' Review of Papers, 1979; 1980 March; Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Women in Love with Prisoners, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Workshops: Proposed on Capital Punishment, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 28 Forms of Deviance, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 60 Minutes, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 1950 FOF, 1941; 1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1951 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 1952 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 1953 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 1954 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 1955 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 1956 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - 1957 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - 1958 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - 1959 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - 1960 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - 1961 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - 1962 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - 1963 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - 1964 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - 1965 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - 1966 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - 1967 FOF, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - 1990 Speaking Engagements, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Death Penalty News Clippings, 1979-1997; 8; 2.8
  The Death Penalty News Clippings are clippings Dr. Bowers collected for a number of years.
  - News Clippings, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1980 January-1980 March (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1980 April-1980 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1980 July-1980 September (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1980 October-1980 December (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1981 January-1981 March (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1981 January-1981 March (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1981 April-1981 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1981 July-1981 September (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1981 October-1981 December (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1982 January-1982 March (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1982 April-1982 June (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1982 July-1982 August (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1982 September-1982 December (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1983 January-1983 May (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1983 July-1983 December (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1984 January-1984 August (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1984 September-1984 December (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1985 January-1985 May (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1985 June-1985 December (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1983-November-1986 February (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1986 January-1986 June (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1986 July-1986 November (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1986 November (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1988 September (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1988 December (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1989 November (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1990 January (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1990 February (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1990 March (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1990 April (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1990 May (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1992 June (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1992 July (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1992 August (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1992 September (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1992 October (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1992 November (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1992 December (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - News Clippings, 1993 January (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - News Clippings, 1993 February (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - News Clippings, 1993 March (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - News Clippings, 1993 April (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings, 1993 May (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings, 1993 June (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - News Clippings, 1993 July (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - News Clippings, 1993 August (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - News Clippings, 1993 September (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - News Clippings, 1993 October (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - News Clippings, 1993 November (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - News Clippings, 1993 December (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - News Clippings, 1994 January (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - News Clippings, 1994 February (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - News Clippings, 1994 March (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - News Clippings, 1994 April (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - News Clippings, 1994 May (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - News Clippings, 1994 June (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - News Clippings, 1994 July (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - News Clippings, 1994 August (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - News Clippings, 1994 September (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1994 October (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1994 November (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1994 December (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1995 January (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1995 February (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1995 March (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1995 April (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1995 May (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1995 June (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1995 July (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1995 August (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1995 September (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1995 October (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1995 November (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1995 December (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1996 January (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1996 March (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1996 April (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1996 May (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1996 June (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1996 July (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1996 August (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1996 September (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1996 October (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1996 November (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1996 December (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1997 January (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1997 February (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1997 October (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1997 November (Box 4, Folder 17)